

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Eindhoven, the Netherlands

□ (+31) 6 4820 9406 | 🗷 cas@eliens.co | 🖸 cascer1 | 🖹 cas-eliëns | 🛅 caseliens | 🚭 cascer1

"Truth can only be found in one place: the code."

Summary_

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history in backend development.

Skilled in Java, PHP, Deployment, and Customer Service. Strong software professional with a Bachelor of Information & Communication Technology focused in Computer Software Engineering and Cyber Security from Fontys Hogescholen.

Experience _____

Sharegroup b.v.

Developer Dec 2017 - Current

- Develop API back-end for Soundshare platform
- Implement collaborative product recommendations

Duco HostingEindhoven, NL

 OWNER
 Apr 2013 - Mar 2018

- · Managed hosting infrastructure and servers
- Linux server security and configuration
- Managed DNS and other domain configurations

ISAAC Eindhoven, NL

INTERN JAVA DEVELOPMENT Aug 2016 - Jan 2017

- · Developed automated API documentation tooling for RAML and Swagger
- Researched iDin authentication for secure financial logins

HEMA Eindhoven, NL

Sales Representative Nov 2010 - current

- Maintain proper stocking levels for internal consumables like receipt paper and office supplies
- · Applied and maintained in-store promotional material

Education

Fontys Hogeschool ICT Eindhoven, the Netherlands

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING 2014 - 2018

- · Completed courses toward a bachelor in Software Engineering
- Participated in the Fontys ICT Delta excellence program

Extracurricular Activity _____

reddit.com/r/diabetes

COMMUNITY MODERATOR May 2017 - current

- Moderate popular chat platform for a diabetes support group.
- Provide helpful insights and support in diabetes care.
- Moderate the r/diabetes community on Reddit.
- Help protect the community from unwelcome content.

Cas Eliëns · Résumé

online



Why every diabetic should switch to a closed-loop system

medium.com/@cas.eliens/bd520c732dc1

Apr 21, 2018

- Describe first-hand experiences with insulin pump automation
- Explain safety precautions in OpenAPS insulin pump automation software